dangerous-business.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy / Disclosures

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally identifiable information (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read this privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how A Dangerous Business collects, uses, protects, or otherwise handles your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this website.

**What personal information do I collect from the people that visit my blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on this site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do I collect information?**

I collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter or email updates, make a purchase, respond to a survey, or otherwise enter information on this site.

**How do I use your information?**

I may use the information collected from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for my newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user's experience and to allow me to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve the website in order to better serve you.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails regarding the site or other products and services.

I will never sell or trade your information, and if at any time you want to unsubscribe from any email communication, you can do so by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**How do I protect visitor information?**

This website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit as safe as possible.

No personal information is stored on the site or its backend at any time.

**Do I use ‘cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, a site may use cookies to help remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables me to provide you with improved services. I also use cookies to help compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that I can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

A Dangerous Business mainly uses cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. I also use trusted third party services that track this information on my behalf, such as Google Analytics. (To learn exactly how Google uses your data in this case, please go here: [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).)

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at my discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on this website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of my site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Contacting me**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact me at adangerousbusiness [at] gmail [dot] com.

## Disclosures

**Partnerships**

From time to time, A Dangerous Business works with travel brands and tourism boards in order to experience and promote specific destinations, tours, activities, etc. Sometimes I receive compensation as part of these partnerships, which can take the form of cash, credit, or free activities, tours, gear, accommodation, flights, etc.

No matter who foots the bill, though, you can rest assured that I will ALWAYS give honest and unbiased reviews of my experiences. When I partner with a brand or tourism board, I still retain complete editorial control. I also never work with brands that I do not believe in or support – anything I recommend to you, I would (and do) use myself.

All such partnerships/exchanges are disclosed in each and every relevant blog post.

**Affiliate links**

In some instances, I may include affiliate links in posts where I recommend specific gear, tours, or activities. If you purchase something through one of my affiliate links, I receive a small commission at no extra cost to you. These links are always disclosed.

Among other programs, A Dangerous Business is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

_Last Edited on 5-15-2017_
